bitcoin.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy – Bitcoin.com

**Last Updated: 21 September 2015**

We pledge to meet fully, and where possible exceed, internationally recognized standards of personal data privacy protection. Bitcoin.com may change the terms of this policy from time to time. You should check the page to make sure you are agree with the terms.

#### We May Collect the Following Information:

  * Your browsing data obtained through the use of cookies;
  * The email address you voluntarily provide us by opting in to our mailing list.

#### What We Do with the Information We Gather:

We analyze the information we gather to learn more about how Bitcoin.com visitors use the site and  
what content they prefer.

We may use the information to analyze activity and determine preferences of Bitcoin.com visitors from  
a particular location as determined by IP address. At the same time, we encourage the use TOR or a  
proxy as a method for users to opt-out of this form of data collection.

If you provide us your email and opt-in, we may send you newsletters and emails about other  
organizations, events, products or other information which we think you may find interesting using the  
email address which you have provide.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages users find useful and which ones they do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

The only personal information we presently collect is your email address should you choose to provide it for our mailing list. You may choose to restrict the our use of your mailing list by unsubscribing.
